A Guide to the L. T. Christian Funeral Home Records, 1912-1986
Library of Virginia
- Mayo, Lalla, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Mayo, Louis Randolph, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Mayo, Luck Garnett, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Mayo, Lucy L., 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Mayo, Mary Maury, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Mayo, Robert W. B., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Mayo, William S. P., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Mazurek, Thomas C., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Mazzarella, Alfred, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- McAdams, Elbert, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- McAden, Willard Warren, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- McAllister, Annie Matilda, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- McAllister, James Gray, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- McAllister, Joseph Thompson, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- McAllister, Louise, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- McAllister, Meta Russell, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- McAnally, Nannie Wall, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- McAuley, Benton Willis, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- McBain, Lucy Braxton Harwood, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- McBain, William F., 1944 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- McBride, Ann, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- McBride, Frederick B., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- McBride, Marcellus D., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- McBride, Mary E., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- McBryde, William Waller, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- McCaden, Margaret Rutherford, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- McCall, Bertie Massingill, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- McCann, Columbia, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- McCann, James A., 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- McCann, Louise, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- McCarey, Cecil, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- McCarthy, Daniel Stephen, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- McCarthy, Deborah Anthony, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- McCarthy, Edward, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- McCarthy, Helen Emellia, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- McCarthy, John, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- McCarthy, Julian Parker, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- McCarthy, Lillian Binford, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- McCarthy, Margaret Phillips, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- McCarthy, Mary Lavonne, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- McCarty, Jean Galbreth, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- McCarty, Mary Lavonne, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- McClellan, William Dodson, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- McClintock, C. E., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- McCloud, Cora Lyon, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- McCluer, Barton Bates, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- McCluer, Robert Watson, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- McCluer, Virginia Chapin, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- McConnell, Harry Moore, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- McConnell, Herbert Logan, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- McConnell, Raymond D., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- McCoy, Henry Pendleton, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- McCracken, Anne Roberts, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- McCracken, Folger Pitts, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- McCraw, Richie Spotswood, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- McCrea, Mary C., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- McCreery, Elizabeth Peterkin, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- McCreery, Nancy Werth, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- McCue, Howard McDowell, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- McCue, John Frederick Morton, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- McCue, Mary Allen, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- McCulloch, Norman Bowman, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- McCullough, Arthur Kemp, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- McCullough, Orlando Mitchell, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- McCullough, Virginia Hayes, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- McDill, Joseph M., 1981 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- McDonald, Robert Gaines, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- McDonald, Wilhelmina Fox, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- McDonough, Kathreen, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- McDowell, Alfred Henderson, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- McDowell, Emily J., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- McDowell, Inez Brown, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- McDowell, William James, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- McElrath, Maria Jane, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- McElroy, Alice Wilson, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- McElroy, Francis Cassidy, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- McElroy, John Lee, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- McElroy, Paul Irving, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- McFadden, James, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- McFadden, Mary Ethel Lewis, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- McFaden, Lillie Caldwell, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- McFarlane, James, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- McGeachy, Daniel Patrick, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- McGeachy, Lilia English, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- McGee, Carol May Jackson, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- McGee, Lois Johnson, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- McGill, Edward, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- McGill, Mildred Saunders, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- McGilvra, Kittredge Scott, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- McGilvray, Bessie, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- McGilvray, Bessie Giggins, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- McGinnis, Elizabeth Fergusson, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- McGinniss, William Berkeley, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- McGovern, Harvey, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- McGovern, Mary F., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- McGrath, Ellen E., 1972 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- McGrath, Mary R., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- McGrath, Richard Allen, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- McGrath, Robert A., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- McGraw, Craig Ray, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- McGuire, Helen Nolting, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- McGuire, Hunter Holmes, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- McGuire, Hunter Holmes, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- McGuire, Ruth Robertson, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- McGuire, Stuart, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- McIlwaine, Henry Read, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- McIlwaine, Mary W., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- McIlwaine, Richard, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- McIntyre, Anna J., 1973 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- McIntyre, Daniel Monroe, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- McIntyre, Edward Duncan, Jr., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- McIver, Harriett Roderick, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- McKee, James Braxton, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- McKee, Martha Lloyd, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- McKee, William Scott, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- McKeel, Daniel Walter, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- McKeel, Katherine DeLarue, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- McKeel, Minnie Ada, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- McKenna, [infant] of Archie, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- McKenney, A. Carlton, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- McKenney, Florence Carlton, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- McKenney, Helen Norris, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- McKillip, Rebecca, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- McKim, Alice, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- McKim, William Ormand, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- McKinney, Clifford Bernard, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- McKinney, Helen L., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- McLamb, Meta Fay, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- McLarin, Esther Mussadus, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- McLaughlin, Charles Madison, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- McLaws, Anna Norwood Davis, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- McLelland, Benjamin, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- McLelland, Benjamin W., 1948 (disinterred 1950) (Box 10, Folder 20)
- McLeod, Alfred Marshall, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- McLeod, Mildred Morrell, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- McLeod, Nancy C., 1933 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- McLeod, Robert Nall, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- McLeod, Virginia, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- McMinn, Hattie B., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- McMullan, Charles G., 1982 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- McNamara, Selina Hayward, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- McNeil, Harold (Duke), 1971 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- McNeill, Elmo S. [infant], 1933 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- McNelis, Cornelia, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- McNiven, Harry Bright, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- McNiven, Jeannette, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- McNiven, Margaret Brunet, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- McPhail, Alice Johnson, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- McPherson, Winfield Travers, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- McRae, Ella, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- McRae, Julia, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- McRea, Archibald M., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- McRee, Elizabeth Goodridge S., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- McRee, Fergus, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- McRee, Frances J., 1967 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- McRee, Johnston, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- McRee, Margaret Snow, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- McSparran, Erasmus C., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- McSwain, Dolier Irene, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- McVeigh, Isabel, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- McVey, Henry Hanna, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- McVey, Joanne H., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- McWhorter, Bessie Belle Gammon, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Meachum, Walter Eugene, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Mead, Aline Jennings, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Mead, Ernest C., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Mead, George Otis, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Mead, Lillie Jennings, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Meade, Ann Barksdale, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Meade, Edward R., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Meade, Everard B., 1958 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Meade, Jane H., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Meade, Kate Fontaine, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Meade, Lucy Skelton, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Meade, Marianne E., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Meade, Nancy Spencer, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Meade, Nellie Prior, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Meade, Richard Eggleston, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Meade, Richard Hardaway, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Meanley, Louise Kidd, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Meek, James William, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Meeteer, Agnes, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Megargel, Margery Knowles, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Melick, Daisy Bowles, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Melick, Ira, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Mercer, Elizabeth Walker, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Mercer, Roger W., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Mercer, Sallie Taurman, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Merchant, James Ratcliffe, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Meredith, [infant], 1940 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Meredith, Alice Morson, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Meredith, C. V., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Meredith, Eugene Coles, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Meredith, John Washington, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Meredith, Kate Watson, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Meredith, Rosalie Elizabeth, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Meredith, Sophie, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Meredith, Wyndham R., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Meriwether, Evelyn Page, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Merrell, Vincent, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Merrick, Rebecca V., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Merrill, Eleanor Brown, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Messer, James Albert, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Metcalf, Robert Leland, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Metcalfe, Hayes McDowell, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Mettert, Mary Christina, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Metzger, Lillie Dansey, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Meyer, Camille, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Meyer, Julian A. S., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Meyer, Margaret L., 1972 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Michael, Alice Anderson, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Michaels, Bernice Hilsman, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Michaels, Urlwin O., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Michaux, Byrd Sublett, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Michaux, James Madison, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Michaux, Martha Whitehead, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Michaux, Minnie, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Michaux, Stuart, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Michaux, Stuart N., 1984 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Michaux, Victorine Aldridge, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Michaux, Wilhelmina Henry, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Michaux, William Walthall, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Michel, Hazelle S., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Mickelboro, William Louis, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Middlebrook, Auretta, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Miles, Elizabeth Walton, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Miles, Wade M., 1944 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Millan, Frank Adelbert, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Miller, [infants] daughters of Donald G., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Miller, Annie Maude B., 1969 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Miller, Crosby Park, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Miller, Effie Kennedy, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Miller, Eliza Ingram, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Miller, Emma Bouknight, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Miller, Emma H., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Miller, Gray, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Miller, Henry C., Jr., 1980 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Miller, Hugh, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Miller, Iola Sorey, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Miller, James Alexander, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Miller, James McGilvany, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Miller, Jennie F. Watkins, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Miller, Leland Long, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Miller, Louise Seaman, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Miller, Louise Trent, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Miller, Lucille Nelson, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Miller, Mary Elizabeth, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Miller, Mary Houston, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Miller, Minnie Deaton, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Miller, Nancy H., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Miller, Paul Earnest, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Miller, Rose Ferrell, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Miller, Sara Drake, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Miller, Thelma Tignor, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Miller, Turner Ashby, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Miller, Vivienne G., 1983 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Miller, William Charles, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Miller, William McClanahan, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Miller, William McClanahan, n. d. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Miller, William Read, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Miller, Willis Dance, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Millner, Mattie Puryear, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Mills, Grace Phauf, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Mills, Jesse Burnice, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Mills, May Brauer, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Mills, Morgan R., Jr., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Mills, Virginia Wickham, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Milnes, Alice M., 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Miltz, Minnie, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Mimms, Margaret, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Mines, Anna Beatrice, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Minnegerode, Augusta Carter, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Minnigh, Morton L., 1983 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Minor, Annie Mortimer, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Minor, Claude Dryden, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Minor, Frances Ellen Jackson, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Minor, Gene Salzman, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Minor, George Gilmer, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Minor, Helen Flippen, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Minor, Jane, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Minor, Kate Farmer, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Minor, Lena Fraces Robertson, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Minor, Lucy H., 1984 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Minor, Ophelia Yarbrough, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Minor, Percy George, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Minor, Virginia Hannah, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Minor, William Yarborough, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Minter, Edgar Winn, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Minter, George Wiley, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Minter, Mary Ella Shelton, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Minter, Maude Davis, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Minter, Vivian Rosemond H., 1979 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous/Unidentified, 1928-1943 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Miskimon, Mary B. Mae, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Miskimon, Roy R., 1961 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Mitchell, Alice Broadus, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Mitchell, Betty Boyd, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Mitchell, Elizabeth Blair, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Mitchell, Forest J., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Mitchell, Julia Carlton, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Mitchell, Mary, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Mitchell, Owen Overton, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Mitchell, Rachell Anne, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Mitchell, Robert E., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Mitchell, Robert Lee, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Mitchell, Robert Leland, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Mitchell, Samuel Chiles, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Mitchell, Suzie Brook, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Mix, Frank R., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Modlin, John Reid, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Modlin, Patricia Taylor Jenkins, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Moffett, Charles Williams, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Moffett, Edna Virginia, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Moffett, Elvira E., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Moffett, Ernest Lyle, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Moffett, Lelia Austin, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Moffett, Mark Hawkins, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Moffett, N. Crawford, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Moffett, Nellie Braxton, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Moll, William John, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Moncure, Bettie Ashby, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Moncure, James A., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Moncure, Maria Gray, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Moncure, Marie Louise Pollard, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Moncure, Mary Ayres, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Moncure, Michael Wallace, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Moncure, Page, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Moncure, Virginia Buchanan, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Mondy, Emma Virginia, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Mondy, Joseph Henry, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Mondy, Mary, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Mondy, Nannie Murray, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Mondy, Willie Burrows, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Monehan, James, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Monroe, Rae Smith, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Montague, Anne Leiper, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Montague, Frank L., Jr., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Montague, Hill, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Montague, James Wesley, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Montague, Jeremiah Judson, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Montague, John Henry, Jr., 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Montague, Katharine Minor, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Montague, Lillie B., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Montague, Mary Winston, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Montague, Mary Wortley, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Montague, Meredith Fox, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Montague, Wesley C., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Monteith, Caroline Weaver, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Monteith, Jimmie Waters, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Monteith, Robert Palmer, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Montgomery, Joseph B., Jr., 1972 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Montgomery, Joseph Browne, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Montgomery, Margaret Gibson, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Moody, Margaret Lynch, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Moody, Mary Kirkpatrick, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Moody, William Robert, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Mooers, Roberta Medley, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Moon, Celestine, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Moon, Emmett Luck, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Moon, Jacob Luther, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Moon, John Martin, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Moon, Mary Heath, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Moone, Charles Wesley, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Moore, Alice Gennet, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Moore, Andrew Jackson, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Moore, C. Lee, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Moore, Caroline Willingham, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Moore, Carrie L., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Moore, Dorothy Brown, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Moore, Dorothy Leonard, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Moore, Earl Lee, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Moore, Elizabeth Haynes, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Moore, Eva Thomas, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Moore, Helen Gray Gregory, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Moore, Hermine DeVoss, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Moore, Irma, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Moore, James Clifton, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Moore, James Garlick, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Moore, Josephine P., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Moore, Julia Grant, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Moore, L. K., 1958 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Moore, Leta Lucille, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Moore, Linnie Tucker, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Moore, Louise Havermeyer, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Moore, Maria Moncure, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Moore, Marie Dunlop, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Moore, Mary Alexander, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Moore, Mary Cornelia, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Moore, Mary E. Pearson, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Moore, Mary Irwin, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Moore, Mary Louise, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Moore, Moncure Edward, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Moore, Oscar Ryland, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Moore, Paul Joseph, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Moore, Roderick Dunn, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Moore, Rosa Christabell, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Moore, Theadora S., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Moore, Thomas Jefferson, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Moore, Thomas Justin, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Moore, Viola May, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Moore, Virginia, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Moore, Virginia Tabb, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Moore, Walter Verner, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Moore, Walter Wagner, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Moore, Walter Wagner, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Moore, Warner, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Moore, Warner, Jr., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Moorefield, William Singleton, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Moose, William G., 1974 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Moran, Michelle Lynne [infant], 1967 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Mordecai, Augusta, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Mordecai, Charlotte Meade, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Mordecai, Helen Norwood, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Mordecai, John B., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Mordecai, Mary Magill Randolph, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Mordecai, Rosina, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Mordecai, Thomas N., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Morecock, Edith P., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Morecock, Howard M., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Morel, Betty Sparrow, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Morey, Mary C., 1979 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Morgan, Branch, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Morgan, Branch Beale, 1938 (disinterred 1964) (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Morgan, Ethel Tyler, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Morgan, Flavius Glinn, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Morgan, George Dwight (also see G. S. Morgan in box 24), 1970 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Morgan, Grace, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Morgan, Grace S. (also see George D. Morgan in box 30), 1943 (disinterred 1964) (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Morgan, Hope A. (also see George Dwight Morgan), 1970 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Morgan, Hope Alice, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Morgan, Kitty Settle, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Morgan, Marietta McNeill, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Morgan, Milton Ritchie, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Morgan, Olive Branch, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Morgan, Olive Branch, 1964 (disinterred) (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Morgan, Richard D., 1908 (disinterred 1964) (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Morgan, Samuel Tate, Jr., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Morgan, William Pierce, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Morhart, Charles Christian, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Morice, Marie Brown, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Morrell, Helene Miller, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Morris, Annie Virginia, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Morris, Bessy Gordon, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Morris, Carrie V., 1932 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Morris, Chapman Wilson, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Morris, Charles N., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Morris, Ellen G., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Morris, Emily Taylor, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Morris, Emma Marcella, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Morris, Frederick Miller, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Morris, George Harrison, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Morris, Herman W., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Morris, Inez Talley, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Morris, James W., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Morris, Kittie Miller, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Morris, L. Z., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Morris, Leon M. "Lin", 1965 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Morris, Mary Fitzhugh, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Morris, Matilda Latimore, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Morris, Nannie Evelyn, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Morris, Owen, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Morris, Phoebe Lee, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Morris, Roger Lynn, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Morris, Sallie B., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Morris, Sophia, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Morris, Susan P., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Morris, Virginia, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Morris, William, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Morrisette, Charles White, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Morrison, Alfred Hill, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Morrison, Bertha Louise, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Morrison, Katie Moore, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Morton, Alla Hamilton, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Morton, Clarissa C., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Morton, David C., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Morton, Douglas Vass, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Morton, Elizabeth Booker, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Morton, Ellen Fontaine, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Morton, Francis W., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Morton, James, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Morton, John Brightwell, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Morton, Lucy Branch, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Morton, Lucy Walters, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Morton, Margaret Brundige, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Morton, Mary Elizabeth, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Morton, Myrtle Evelyn Cook, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Morton, Nell Montgomery, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 17)